

IT SYSTEMS ANALYST · SECURITY ENTHUSIAST

49 Greenway North, Albany, NY 12208

□ (518) 764-3567 | ☑ chravid092@gmail.com | □ Chrisdav92 | 匝 chris-david-70988010b

Education

The College of Saint Rose

Albany, NY

MASTERS IN COMPUTER INFORMATION SCIENCES, 4.0 GPA

December 2016

The College of Saint Rose

Albany, NY

ACCELERATED BACHELORS IN COMPUTER SCIENCES, 3.5 GPA

December 2016

Hudson Valley Community College

Troy, NY

ASSOCIATES IN COMPUTER SCIENCES, 3.6 GPA

May 2014

Experience

Martin, Harding & Mazzotti, LLP

Schenectady, NY

IT Systems Analyst

June 2017 - Present

- Instrumental in implementation of VPN for remote staff.
- Create and maintain end user technical documentation using LaTeX.
- Streamlined PC image process.
- Respond to and resolve tickets raised by staff as sole on-site IT personnel.
- Work closely with outside IT consultants and vendors.
- Manage Active Directory, Office 365 and various business-specific systems.
- Provide advisement on IT solutions to Management Team and firm Partners.
- Consulted with the Partners and several head of departments on safe computer usage.
- Quickly adapted to role due to transition of IT management at start of employment.
- Provide on-site and remote technical support to over 130 employees across 6 locations

CWA Threat Within

Albany, NY

Cyber Risk Analyst Intern

Jan 2017 - May 2017

- Installed a Kali Linux VM to test out security tools
- Knowledge and practice in producing executive briefing material/memos
- Knowledge and practice in producing succinct briefing videos on the current situation, the derived problems and implications and what actions are being taken to mitigate, respond or defend against future incidents.
- Contextual awareness and knowledge of Cyber security threat landscapes
- Utilized the National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) Cybersecurity Framework

Vascular Birthmarks Foundation

Colonie, NY

THE STEER ST

Jan 2015 - Jan 2017

- Worked on first ever CME accredited website for a non-profit medical organization
- Worked on both front end and back end parts of site, including overall site appearance, classes, modules as well as editing source code
- Contributed in board meetings concerning website development
- Worked in compliance with HIPAA

The College of Saint Rose

Albany, NY

STUDENT SUPPORT TECHNICIAN

June 2015 - June 2017

- Rollout of computers
- Troubleshooted computer issues for students and faculty
- · Helped with a database of computer systems with serial numbers, and with what image was placed on the computers
- Windows/Mac OS installation along with managing accounts
- Go-to person to train new technicians

IT Systems Analyst · Security Enthusiast

49 Greenway North, Albany, NY 12208

□ (518) 764-3567 | ☑ chravid092@gmail.com | □ Chrisdav92 | 匝 chris-david-70988010b

CommerceHub June 19, 2018

ALBANY, NY

Job Application for Information Technology Specialist (Multiple positions)

Dear Mr./Ms./ Recruiting Representative,

About Me_

My name is Chris P. David and I believe that my experience in the realm of computers and my passion for Computer Science makes me an ideal candidate for any of these positions at the state. As a recent College graduate I have a very solid background in Computer Sciences. You state in the posting that you want someone who gets the job done while working with others towards a common goal, as well as someone who will bring not only a great work ethic but someone who others can work along with. Throughout my 5 years in college, not only did I work very hard for my Degree but I also worked two jobs, as an Student IT tech who took on responsibilities of a full time staff-member but also as an IT Specialist for a Not-for profit foundation in which I dealt with HIPAA compliance. Both of these jobs required me to be very specific to details while also paying attention to any issues that may arise at any time. In terms of pressure, my first job out of College I essentially adapted due to the transition of IT management and had to adapt in a matter of a month to provide support for a multitude of users at various locations. I manage not only 5 locations, but worked with an outside consulant team to address any issued that arrived in a timely manner.

Why Me? _____

As the 1st generation of my family to come to America and graduate with an Advanced Degree, I would say I worked hard all my life, in terms of learning various subjects but also becoming someone people can depend on. I love computers in general and as a kid I always wanted to get on my dad's computer, in which I learned how to get around his security password. From there I cultivated my desire to learn about computer science and it wasn't until my last years in my program in which I was able to get into a Cyber Security Internship where the spark of Computer Security was re-kindled and I started to learn as much as I could about it. Though I still consider myself a new person to this world, my hard work ethic and overall passion will make a strong and immediate impact at the state. I am excited about the opportunity to join the team. Thank you for your time and consideration.

Sincerely,

Chris P. David